William Howard Taft IV Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Government File, 1958-1989 (Box 4-74)
  - Presidential Transition (1980), 1958-1981 (Box 72-74)
    - Department of Defense (Box 72)
      - Background material
        - Van Crevald, Martin, "Fighting Power: German Military Performance, 1914-1945," 1980
      - Final activity report, 1980
      - Memoranda, 1980-1981
    - Executive branch reorganization, 1976-1980, undated
    - Spending Control Task Force
      - Budget cutting proposals, 1980, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence and background material, 1979-1981, (2 folders) (Box 74)
- Miscellany, 1960-1988 (Box 74-85)
  Law office files, appointment books, calendars, case studies, college term papers, draft book chapters, subject files, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or type of material and thereunder chronologically.
  - Appointment books and calendars (Box 74)
    - 1972-1974, (5 folders)
    - 1975-1981, (7 folders) (Box 75)
    - 1982-1983, (2 folders, 2 volumes) (Box 76)
    - 1984-1985, (3 folders, 2 volumes) (Box 77)
    - 1986-1988, (4 folders) (Box 78)
  - Biographical material, 1965-1976, undated (Box 79)
  - Family, 1975-1976, 1984-1988, undated, (3 folders)
  - Franks, Jane Lakes, and Tom Ehrlich, "Planning for Justice," 1976-1981
  - Humor, undated
  - Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
    - Horan, Cynthia, "Caspar Weinberger and Welfare Reform," 1977
    - Jernigan, David, "Controlling AFDC Error Rates," 1982
  - Leva, Hawes, Symington, Martin, and Oppenheimer, Washington, D.C. (Box 80)
    - Chronological file
      - Feb. 1977-Mar. 1978, (7 folders)
      - Apr. 1978-Dec. 1979, (7 folders) (Box 81)
      - 1980-Feb. 1981, (4 folders) (Box 82)
    - District of Columbia Judicial Planning Committee
      - "1979 Plan for Improvement of the Judiciary in the District of Columbia"
      - Subcommittee on the workload of the District of Columbia court of appeals
        - Background material, 1978-1979, undated
        - Final report, 1979
        - Tentative report, 1979
    - Energy policy, 1977 (Box 83)
    - McGraw-Hill conference on retirement, 1977-1978
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1978
  - Passports and other travel documents, 1960-1964
  - Politics
    - Boston, Mass., 1968
    - Republican party, 1977-1980, (3 folders)
  - Smith, Bryon E., Jr., "The Anti-Ballistic Missile: Political and Military Considerations," 1968
  - Speeches and writings
    - College term papers
      - 1962-1963, (2 folders)
      - 1964-1966, (5 folders) (Box 84)
    - "Recent Developments in Social Welfare Law and the Doctrine of Separation of Powers," 1977
    - "A Social Welfare Policy for Americans"
      - Chapters, circa 1979
      - Correspondence, notes, and research material, 1977-1979, undated
    - Speech, St. Joseph College, Rensselaer, Ind., 1980 (Box 85)
    - "Tax Incentives for Specific Investments," 1969
    - Taft Broadcasting Co., 1970
    - Vietnam conflict and the draft, 1967-1968
    - Washington Opera, Washington, D.C., 1977-1981, (4 folders)